Welcome back to my series recreating
Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors, but low
calorie and high protein. This is the
chocolate chip cookie dough blizzard.
Let me show you how to make it. If
you've been following me for a while
now, you know that this is just my
classic vanilla base. You're just going
to need some fat-ree milk. I always use
the Fairlife one, sweetener, zantham
gum, salt, vanilla bean paste, and then
you can just blend that all together and
then throw it in your freezer for at
least 16 hours. Once it's completely
frozen, you can take it out and run it
under hot water for about a minute. And
then throw it in your creamy on the
light ice cream setting. It'll probably
come out a little bit powdery. Mine was
decent, but I still wanted to scrape
down the sides and just ensure there
were no huge ice chunks in there. And
while I did this, I carved a hole out in
the center for my mixins. And this is
the key. I use these highkey soft baked
cookies. You can use whatever kind of
chocolate chip cookies. You can use
cookie dough, little cookie dough bites,
whatever you want to do. Run on the
mixing setting and boom, you have a
Dairy Queen Blizzard packed with
protein.